equinix.com 2019-03-07

# Privacy Statement | Equinix

Equinix is committed to complying with data protection laws applicable to its business, including the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). We recognise that ensuring GDPR standards are embedded in our day to day operations where we handle Personal Data of EU citizens is a key GDPR compliance requirement.

Equinix Inc. and its affiliated companies in the United States and worldwide, in its three operating regions, the Americas, EMEA and Asia-Pacific (“Equinix,” or “we,” “us,” “our,”) are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognise your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) that you may share with us.

### Personal Data

Personal Data means any information which enables us to identify you and which is related to an identified or identifiable natural person (also known as a ‘data subject’), such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier to one or more factors specific to the identity of that natural person.

### Use of Personal Data

Equinix collects and uses your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to provide you or the business with whom you are associated with certain personalised services;
  * to support activities such as customer service, marketing, product and service development, dissemination of investor information and recruiting;
  * to inform you or the business with whom you are associated of our products and services and provide you with our latest information and news about the Equinix group;
  * to enable you to contact Equinix and for us to respond to you;
  * to carry out from time to time certain satisfaction surveys about how Equinix is doing; and
  * to analyse the use of this website by you in order to develop and enhance the services we may provide to the business with whom you are associated, and to facilitate subsequent use of this website.

### Disclosure of Personal Data

We will not disclose your Personal Data to anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may share your Personal Data with companies within the Equinix group.

We may share Personal Data with our contracted service providers, vendors, suppliers and our third-party processors such as third-party marketing service providers acting on our behalf and under our instructions. These providers are authorized to use your Personal Data only as necessary to provide the services. Equinix is focusing its efforts to ensure that they handle this Personal Data in light with the high standards of applicable data protection rules, including GDPR.

In the event that you [opt in for receiving promotional materials](http://info.equinix.com/PM-ID-Authentication-EN.html), we may from time to time notify you of special promotions, new products or services, or other information that may interest you.

We reserve the right to disclose any such Personal Data if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with applicable law, or protect the rights, property or safety of Equinix, its employees, customers, or the public.

### Transfer of Personal Data

Considering the global reach of Equinix’s business, your Personal Data may be transferred between our group companies in the Americas, EMEA and Asia-Pacific regions, including locations where the data privacy legislation may differ from that in your country.

Equinix has in place all appropriate legitimization measures to ensure the validity of Personal Data transfers to countries in which there is not a similar level of protection as in your country and as required under applicable data protection and privacy laws. Those legitimization measure include the entry into appropriate inter-company data transfer agreements based on the European Standard Contractual Clauses (“EU Model Clauses”) and the implementation of Binding Corporate Rules as defined under European Union regulations.

### User Consent

By using this web site and other online portals, you consent to the to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and to our processing of your Personal Data for the purposes described above as well as those explained where Equinix collects Personal Data on the web or in other online portals.

Where required, we will be supplementing this consent with a more specific statement at the time that we specifically obtain the Personal Data from you.

Regarding the use of Personal Data for marketing purposes as outlined above, you may always update your consent preferences at our [Customer Preference Center](http://info.equinix.com/PM-ID-Authentication-EN.html). Every marketing email from us contains instructions on how to opt out of receiving further marketing emails from the Equinix. Additionally, you may [unsubscribe here](http://info.equinix.com/Preference-Management-Center-WW?tab=subscriptions) or by contacting us using the information in the “Contacting Us" section below.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Equinix reserves the right to change the terms of its Privacy Policy at any time. If we do change this Privacy Policy, we will take steps to indicate that the Policy has been updated on this web site. Equinix will provide notification of the changes to this Privacy Policy through access to its web site.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID, which the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only Personal Data a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of Equinix’s web site use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this to determine the usefulness of Equinix’s information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. Equinix does not correlate this information with Personal Data about individual users, nor does it share this information or sell it to any third party.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the website.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, clickstream patterns and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your online experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Data for trends and statistics.

### Your Rights

Subject to applicable data protection rules, you are entitled to a right of access to Personal Data that Equinix collects about you, a right of rectification and deletion and a right to restrict and object to the processing of your Personal Data on legitimate grounds. We also ensure that Equinix has high level procedures in place to deal with any suspected breach of data security, unauthorized access or disclosure, or loss of Personal Data. We guarantee that your rights in the unlikely event of a data breach are fully respected.

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Data to Equinix. The notice we intend to provide where Equinix collects Personal Data on the web site or on the applicable online portal should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Data we request, you can still visit most of Equinix’s web pages, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our continued interaction with you.

You should be aware that if you delete or restrict our access and use of certain Personal Data we use to provide contracted services to you or the business with whom you are associated, it may have an impact upon our ability to continue to provide those services to you or the business with whom you are associated.

### Contact Us

To facilitate Equinix’s compliance with GDPR and other applicable data privacy laws world-wide, and to ensure strong and consistent support for data privacy matters within Equinix globally, Equinix has recently established a Privacy Office to manage data privacy compliance for Equinix and to co-ordinate support for customers on data privacy matters.

If you have any query on this Privacy Policy enquiry, or if you wish to exercise any of your rights described above, please contact us at the following email address: [PrivacyOffice@eu.equinix.com](mailto:PrivacyOffice@eu.equinix.com) or write to Peter Waters, Chief Privacy Officer, Equinix Services Limited, 11 Devonshire Square, London EC2M 4YR, United Kingdom.
